#### Contact

crystalda27@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/crystal-d-chafin-msn-aprn-fnp-bc-a96736b6 (LinkedIn) crystalda27.wixsite.com (Portfolio)

#### Top Skills

Healthcare

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

#### Certifications

Registered Nurse Family Nurse Practitioner (FNP) Advanced Practice Registered Nurse

# Crystal D. Chafin, MSN, APRN, FNP-BC

Board Certified Nurse Practitioner

Johnson City, Tennessee Area

#### Summary

Board Certified Nurse Practitioner with a Master of Science in Nursing degree from King University. I am currently working with Trauma/Acute Care Surgical services at Holston Valley Medical Center, and cross covering with Ballad Health Neurosurgery. Prior to this, I worked as a nurse practitioner in nephrology with Regional Kidney Care, credentialed in 4 hospitals, an outpatient dialysis clinic and within the office setting. My background includes over 19 years of experience as an RN/BSN in medical, neuro, and trauma critical care nursing, with a deep passion for patient care. With my experience and dedication to both healthcare and my patients, I hope to not only meet expectations, but exceed them in any position God places me in.

## Experience

Trauma Surgical Services
Board Certified Nurse Practitioner
January 2020 - Present (7 months)
Holston Valley Hospital

Regional Kidney Care- Kingsport, TN Family Nurse Practitioner November 2018 - January 2020 (1 year 3 months) Tri-Cities

Wellmont Health System
Neuro/critical care RN
April 2001 - July 2016 (15 years 4 months)

#### Education

## King University

Master of Science in Nursing, Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2016 - 2018)

## East Tennessee State University

Bachelor of Science in Nursing · (1998 - 2002)